fireboxstove.com 2018-02-01

# Privacy Policy

**GENERAL**

We recognize that our customers, visitors, users, and others (known collectively or individually as "Users") who use our Website value their privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services, and Websites we offer, or by any of our subsidiaries or affiliated companies. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Website.

Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our 'Terms of Service'.

Please note that any comment or other content you post or send to the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. Your messages and other information you make available in public areas of our Website will be seen by people and organizations not related to or controlled by us, and may be used by others to contact you.

Our Privacy Policy applies only to Websites and services that are owned and operated by us. While other Websites may be displayed as links from within our Website, those sites are owned and operated by others, and they may have different privacy policies. When linking from our Website to other Websites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites.

**1\. Information Collection and Use**

We do not require that you register in order to view our products or user comments.

We may collect personal information when you register, when you visit the Website, when you make a purchase, or any time you provide information about yourself. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register, we ask for information such as your name, email address, and other personally-identifying information ("Personal Information"). When you register and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

**2\. Confidentiality and Security**

We use commercially reasonable technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Information you transmit to us. You do so at your own risk.

We limit access to Personal Information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with Personal Information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**3\. International Users**

If you are a User accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy as incorporated in our Terms of Service, you will be transferring your Personal Information into the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**4\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this policy at any time at our sole discretion and without prior notice. We will strive to notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account and/or by placing a notice on the Website.

**5\. Effective Date**

This Privacy Policy was last modified August 1, 2013.
